

# Mariana Ferreira

PEGA Developer, Plexus Tech

- P July 17, 1995
- (+351) 912220291
- 😯 linkedin.com/in/marianacnferreira
- marianaferreira0717@gmail.com
- Porto, Portugal

# Languages -

- Portuguese
- **English**
- Spanish



## Soft Skills -

- Strategic thinking
- Team work
- Planning
- Organization
- Proactivity
- Communication
- Problem Solving
- Resilience

## Hard Skills

- SQL 📂
- 📂 IBM BPM
- PEGA
- JavaScript
- Phyton
- 📂 SoapUI
- HTML
- Postman
- 📂 Appian
- React

#### About Me

MSc in Biomedical Engineer by University of Minho (2013-2018). I started as a Researcher in IPATIMUP, but soon I realize that it was not a job for me. I am passionate about technology and about using my technical know-how to benefit other people and organisations. As a Padel athlete and a passionate traveler, I have excellent interpersonal skills, enabling me to interact with a wide range of clients. I am an energetic, ambitious person who was developed a mature and responsible approach to any task that I undertake, or situation that I am presented with.

## **Working Experience**

PLEXUS

Plexus Tech

Pega Developer

Nov 2021 - Currently

**SIEMENS** 

SIEMENS SA

Pega Developer

May 2020 - Oct 2021

Development of an Accounts Payable Application and a Purchase Order Application for Siemens SA from USA in a multinational team:

- Development of technical specifications to support the functional requirements and doing bug fixes;
- Participation in the respective release to the production environment and posterior support and maintenance of the application.



**NOVABASE FSI** 

**IBM BPM Developer** 

Jan 2019 - April 2020

IBM BPM support and maintenance in AdvanceCare.

Development of an Account Maintenance Application for Banco Atlântico (Angola):

- Experience in developing Business Process Definitions using various modeling patterns and doing bug fixes;
- Implementing activities via Human Services, General System Services, Decision Services and Web Services integration's through process designer;
- Participation in software system documentation and respective release to the production environment and posterior Support and maintenance of the application.

### Education

2013 – 2018 Integrated Master in Biomedical Engineer

University of Minho

2010 – 2013 High School - Sciences and Technologies

Externato Ribadouro

### **Certificates**

Appian Appian Developer 5-Day



Cambridge B2 First